

EDUCATION

Full Stack Development

Masai School

04/2022 - 11/2022

Master Degree in Biochemistry

Holkar Science College, Indore 2015 - 2017

Bachelor Degree

Holkar Science College, Indore 2012 - 2015

SKILLS

Tech Stack

JAVA · JavaScript · Html · CSS ·

Spring Boot · MySQL · Hibernate ·

Data Structures and Algorithms ·

Git & Github · NPM

Soft Skils

Problem solving · Responsible ·

Project Management ·

Time Management · Discipline ·

Communication · Teamwork ·

Interpersonal skills

LANGUAGES

Hindi Native ••••

English Proficient

FIND ME ONLINE

in LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/guptag-divya

GitHub

https://github.com/Divya1327

 ■ Twitter

https://twitter.com/DivyaGupta091

Divya Gupta

Full-Stack Web Developer

\$\ +91-8770537819 @ divyagpt1327@gmail.com \$\ \Omega\$ https://divya1327.github.io \$\ \Omega\$ Indore

SUMMARY

Passionate full-stack developer certified from Masai. 1200 hours of hands-on experience to develop many websites/applications. Have a wide range of front-end and back-end skills like HTML, CSS, JAVA, and JS. Build 5+ projects from scratch. Solved more than 300 data structure questions. Looking further to enhance my skills as a future full-stack developer.

PROJECTS

Outlook-India Clone

Cloned Outlook-India website within 5 days along with 3 aspiring developers.

- GitHub Deployed Link.
- Outlook is India's most credible current affairs and news magazine.
- · We used HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery in our project.
- My responsibility was to build Photos, Video and Entertainment Page.
- · I also helped other teammates to achieve their daily task.

Overstock

Cloned Overstock website within 5 days along with 4 aspiring developers.

- GitHub Deployed Link
- Overstock is online retailer for furniture, rugs and decor.
- We used HTML,CSS JavaScript and JSON API in our project.
- My responsibility was to build a part in homepage and add to product in card.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Executive in OA

09/2019 - 09/2021

Pious Laboratories Pvt. Ltd.

Analytical Testing laboratory

- · Handled Schedule Training and Unplanned training.
- Managing Documentation and Data Integrity.
- Managing the production of whole department and making sure product is completed before deadline, Services.

Trainee Executive in Management

08/2017 - 05/2018

Choksi Laboratories Ltd.

Choksi Laboratories Limited, as it is more widely known, is a leading analysis and research group, providing complete solutions for improving quality in Processes, Products:

- Ensured that all the projects are delivered on time within a scope.
- Coordinate internal resources availability and allocation.
- · Develop a detailed plant and track the project process.

INTERESTS

Reading · Learning languages · Trekking · Listening to music · Travelling